you ready to dance están listos para
bailar okay get ready step number one
yeah preparing se para el paso numero
uno turn off your phone
para el celular we're gonna go up to the
39 right vamos ahora ellos no way then
when we get to past the fourth formless
realm y el super ro pasar el cuarto
nivel del Rios informa we'll go to the
lamas okay vamos coño llamas the
emptiness of the number gonna be a
dilemma the emptiness of the llama is
interesting logic we are llamas
interesante because the llama is
supposed to teach you something you
don't know por que se supone que la ma
de tiene que ser algo que no sabes but
you are creating that llama la testa
screen no salaam it's funny right
gracias so you're creating someone to
teach you something you don't know
estas creando are Yankee and seeing ye
algo que no sabes and that's the
emptiness of a llama okay Slavic we are
a llama okay they are coming from you
mean entity how can it be that a llama
which you are creating teach you
something more than you know how can it
be como puede ser que como SPO silicon
avocat estas creando then say me
algo que tú no sabes
wait somebody got clothing on though of
course yeah a second law of karma who
said I said Oh Tim okay second law of
karma hace una ley del Carmen right in
the same way that you can make a lot of
money by helping someone else make a
little money
the la misma and manera que pase you are
a alguien hacer mucho dinero
young viola sell beaucoup then you can
create a llama to pass claro nama who
can teach you something you don't know
the second position your tail go to no
service okay and and that's the
emptiness remember this Islamic wheel a
llama so emptiness of llama doesn't mean
llamas head is empty or something like
maybe it is a llama no significa que la
cabeza la Mustafa see what oh yeah can
we record this lion stands today and
then make it available on the AC our
website yeah okay Loyola vamos a poner
una website por aqui esta camp or
magnificos / - rah rah meatus you know I
would try to make two independent
recordings Avast Obispo namely because
the demons will break one of them okay
okay okay so we're gonna go to that last
step 10 right emptiness meditation vamos
Cyril pass in the middle yes meet us in
the lower cuidado
we could do the emptiness of your
partner who yelled at you last night
podemos many terranova cuidado para que
que take a detour anoche but the
emptiness of your teacher pero la la
cuidad maestro is a big
karma teaching a sunnah Grannis against
a karma and we're going to use the
emptiness of the teacher Eva Moses our
lava cuidado
maestro to review what we learned about
karma para Reposado Kelvin Demoiselle
karma so when we get to the emptiness of
the teacher why we chose the teacher in
condoms Eloqua dal master pork as
coastal maestro maestra because i want
you to go back in in your lifetimes
particular calendar course as we as
Posadas and continue this movie okay he
continued a continuing Canasta película
so within a month it should after a
month of which our disposal mezack we
teacher what's up what's up after a
month of what's up disposing master
what's up this movie about your past
life esta película to via Posada should
be like a Japanese epic you know for our
movie the Makassar Kuna película de
ponerse cuatro horas okay sorry what we
do today I want you to keep doing se que
lo que Haga Noi quiero que los en
haciendo and part of seeing emptiness
repartee persevere aqua directamente is
to see why why were you born here yes
persevere over la razón well motivo la
causa katissa nasarah key what caused
you to be born here because over Nancy
dokie
you know what causes you to meet your
teacher the cow so conservative maestro
that's a meditation on the Wheel of Life
selamat Sen La Rue de la Vida ok so
traditionally seek a traditional
maintain the wheel of life is the
subject after you do the dance of the
line ok they seldom
la la la vie assert their myspace de
hacer la danse early on so really we're
gonna do dance of lion vs. la la la Luna
then we're gonna do emptiness a plumber
local avec qui Dalai Lama and part of
the emptiness of the Lama is where did
they come from
he part L avec qui le llamas there on
the probe II know what was the scene
okay then we'll come back to the llamas
face because it's good luck to stop at
the llama logo or aggressor a masala
curry llama Porky's suerte all the
repeat over and over again
Dola libro repeatin una otra vez that
when you meditate on your llamas face
you can automate the sinner and la cara
- llama focus on the eyes for cutting us
off horse and that the eyes are loving
you that a llama loves submission open
the door clear los que los ojos chairman
three important things coming in the
responses important is you handle one
student in two cappuccinos
honestly I'm payin signals okay so we're
gonna do it
oh it's for me Oh Instant Karma okay so
uh you know we're gonna end it
you almost a finally said let me touch
your on the loving eyes of the teacher
right and also for tomorrow so se llama
then don't forget at the end of the
meditation three three long exhales
don't start moving when I say three and
long exhales don't start doing your
stretch you still have some job to do no
que no se M PS enamelware second olesya
que al final de la metas en cagin tres
largas Axela Sione's AG unless complete
ASIMO ver si por que tiene esta no
trabajando you are doing three long
exhales imagine like a golden light okay
yeah la siesta zexal a Sione's largas
homogeneous una Luz Uralla
if you want to be a big yogi you can do
it out of here instead of out these are
kind of dirty but this is kind of cool
yeah si quiere ser un grande yogi amana
sister Louise or Allah as aqui por que
hacen más imports
the air comes out of here the lightest a
live a las forces imagine it's coming
out of here but o imagine especially
elantris a fool okay and so please don't
move before we do the three breaths of
dedication se que por favor now same way
vanishes today and this
de las Tres respira Sione's exhalation
is a friend are either a car L marry to
MBR low okay and then you know those of
you who want more you'll escape en masse
I'll talk about it after the meditation
okay I'll look on stairs paz de la
meters you there's more men there's more
steps you can do a mass Passos okay